on for a little bit to do today is daily
video which I already did but stream
yard has the option to go live without
actually going live it is put as private
or I don't think it's published I'm
gonna go look back on my channel again
but I couldn't find it there I was like
wait I don't I don't see it here I want
to see how it looked I tomorrow morning
at 11 a.m. I'm hopefully going live on
the new channel on idea cafe I'm writing
out what inviting the people who have
volunteered to be part of it and write
you know kind of basic instructions like
putting their pronouns as after their
name and I really hope we can go live on
that one because you have to wait 24
hours after you create a YouTube channel
and request it and I created the YouTube
channel a few days ago and I thought I
had requested it but today when I went
to go live uncle live but just add it to
the stream yard it wouldn't let me
because it hasn't been okay via and it
was still like you gotta wait 24 hours
but it doesn't countdown so I don't know
whether maybe I did it yesterday evening
but I don't think so I think it should
be 24 hours so I hope the first one is
on the actual channel and not on crowd
democracy but hey if I'm here tomorrow
we will we will do the first one here
and figure out the kinks they're all
friendly people anyway
and I hope some of them I know some of
them I don't know and showcasing but I
also want to link to their back to their
social media and back to their web sites
and there will be a little weird to do
from code democracy where this one has
been growing so slowly I don't see it
necessarily growing fast unless it's
from the idea cafe the idea cafe I have
somewhat of a marketing plan for to have
it grow beyond just commenting on
people's video just basically how I'm
very proud democracy it's like looking
for people who I enjoy watching and and
saying hey come on over be part of the
channel let's have
conversation that creates better world
how about a global cooperative how about
cool we'll use their cooperative and
then people you know in comments there's
a reason I want to have a conversation
with people it's much more conducive to
what we are creating is saying something
and then having someone ask a question
being able to answer the question that
is not what the idea Cafe is the idea
Cafe will be a space where people just
show up and have a conversation about a
meaningful question and so that is what
we are doing tomorrow and I wanted to
come on here quickly and see what it
looks like see how it works when I am on
YouTube I've used stream yard on
periscope and it's cool here there'll be
comments down the side I don't know if
there'll be live comments like the
people who are on I don't know what it
looks like for the participants that are
part of this should be interesting and
so I don't know if they're going to see
comments because although on YouTube
live of course that is one of their
features that you have people commenting
and asking questions because we're
having a conversation that's not really
that conducive to being part of it but
if we can have a conversation and they
aren't watching it live on YouTube they
are part like everyone else can be
having a conversation if they want about
us asking questions suggesting questions
for next time comments on how awesome it
is this exists and that we get to that
we get to create this in the world too
they want to be a part of it offering
future questions but for us to have
likes to wait what is someone saying
it's very distracting and so I like bit
I might have to see the questions but
they won't necessarily see the questions
and lettuce I put them up on the screen
because I see them down the side and
then I can click on them and have them
actually come up on the screen and since
we have half an hour block which I think
I did not stay in the instruction so I
will have that I have yet to send it out
myself to make the Facebook message chat
with all the people who who said who
expressed interest I really wish it was
it was working because I also wanted to
send out the channel so that people
could say
to their fans to their people yes here's
where I'm gonna be having a conversation
tomorrow if you want to come and watch
but maybe it's better for this week that
doesn't happen because we were gonna be
working out some kinks so which I'm all
about doing it as openly and
transparently as possible nothing needs
to be perfect in order to put it out in
the world we're going to we're never
gonna perfect it we're gonna constantly
strive towards making it better and
easier and more enjoyable for the people
who were being part of the conversation
because that's what it's about it's
about it being enjoyable for the people
who are there what made it a powerful
question what couldn't make it a more
powerful question what was in the way
for you to be present lead on video and
streaming a live to the world well sorry
that's part of this plan but later there
will be ways to have this conversation
without being live without being that is
what we're showcasing what how powerful
a conversation is and how amazing any
human being is in order to create the
platform that hosts what we're
showcasing without it needing to be
where anyone can watch it and everyone
might watch it I am really excited I'm
hoping I get enough sleep tonight we'll
see see all right I will see you
tomorrow a better world is on its way
it's like right around the corner this
idea Cafe or who knows maybe the next
one I keep saying this is the thing this
is the thing if something goes wrong and
it falls apart and then but this is the
iteration and this thing has had enough
iterations where it was a Facebook group
and it was like oh people are showing up
it's not part of the algorithm
this isn't about people showing up it's
about me finding people to be part of it
for Wednesday at 11:00 and then we grow
from there as I have people wanting to
be involved and more people wanting to
be involved and I have slots for that
they can talk during a half an hour we
then open up a second half an hour and a
third half an hour and eventually open
it up where it's not just like we're not
starting from Wednesday to let them and
then going for 24/7 and I mean half an
hour increments it'll be you know Friday
at 9:00 a.m. and Tuesday at 4:00 p.m.
and whatever time periods work for
people that can also people have a
comment and all anyone has to do is show
up as they are and offer their
experience their ideas their feelings on
the topic I'm not the topic sorry on the
question that we have generated together
to be powerful and bring forth ideas and
then we are going to figure out what
questions to ask that people want to
answer but also are important that help
us create a better world for ourselves
and for everybody else so that is the
better world we are going to be creating
if you haven't yet already please like
and subscribe hit the little bell here
and on the idea cafe and I will see you
tomorrow